http://fellmanstudio.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for fellmantudio.com and applies solely to information collected by this website. Lynn Fellman is the sole owner fellmantudio.com website. She collects only the information that you voluntarily give her via email or another direct contact from you. She will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted her.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
Unless you ask Lynn not to, she may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. You may opt-out of any future contacts from Lynn by replying to the message or contacting her via Artist (at) fellmantudio.com.
Security
When you submit your comments in the contact form or purchases via the shopping cart, your information is protected online with SSL encrypted safe and secure checkout. The computer in which Lynn stores personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment on an encrypted hard drive and monitored by a VPN service. No one has access to the computer that holds your data other than Lynn. She does not collect sensitive information, such as your credit card data.
Links
This website, fellmantudio.com, contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Lynn is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. When you leave Lynn’s website, you may want to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Menu
